(wall explodes)
(running footsteps)
(walls exploding)
(energy whirring)
(Megumi grunts)
(building exploding)
(cautious music)
(energy flying)
(Megumi grunts)
(energy whirring)
(shikigami slobbering)
[Megumi] There's a bit
of blood on the arrowhead.
Somehow Kamo's technique
allows his arrows to defy physics.
[Noritoshi] You can call more
than one type of shikigami
at a time, right?
Can't say I appreciate you
holding out on me like that.
(intense music)
My Demon Dog's
busy with its task.
What about you? Aren't
you on your last arrow?
Who'll save you if you
pass out from blood loss?
Blood Manipulation.
A technique
manipulating one's blood
and objects imbued
with that blood.
That's fitting for one
of the three major clans
and their love of bloodlines.
There's nothing to worry about.
These are special arrows
I've prepared ahead of time.
Ten Shadows Technique.
One of the Zen'in clan's
hereditary techniques.
It creates ten
types of shikigami
using shadows as its medium.
If only Maki or
Mai had inherited it!
(arrow flying)
(ceiling exploding)
(Megumi grunts)
(Noritoshi punches)
[Megumi] How can he
have that much power?
That was a nice reaction.
But best stay alert!
(Noritoshi grunts)
(Megumi grunts)
[Megumi] Was I too slow to
defend with cursed energy?
With this much speed and power,
it's like he's a
different person now!
The manipulation of blood
isn't limited to just
its shape and motion.
Body temperature,
pulse, red blood cells,
and all the other
components of blood
are all mine to freely control!
Flowing Red Scale!
So now you're doping?
You're very astute.
Though there's no need
to use such a layman's term.
(opening theme music)
(singing in Japanese)
(music fades out)
(bird crowing)
♪ My sword ♪
♪ Has been taken away ♪
♪ From me ♪
[Miwa] Mai's older sister
took it and ran off somewhere.
That woman was fast, too.
And I'm not much of an
asset without my sword,
so obviously she
made the right call.
I wonder if tapioca's
as good as they say.
-(phone vibrating)
-[Miwa] Hm?
(phone vibrating)
It's Mechamaru.
Hi! Useless Miwa here!
[Toge] Sleep.
(Miwa sighs)
(Miwa falls)
(dog panting)
(Miwa snoring)
(dog whining)
[Toge] Return.
(dog dissipates)
(collar zipping)
(Toge gasps)
(suspenseful music)
[Utahime] Ugh, she fell asleep.
-I'm heading out for a bit.
-Huh?
I can't leave her
lying in the woods
with cursed spirits
wandering around, right?
(off key music)
[Noritoshi] What's this?
[Yoshinobu] The
semi-first-grade cursed spirit
that'll be released in the area.
I thought you were
using a second-grade.
I decided that a second-grade
wouldn't be enough.
Hm?
The two schools are not
unified in this, you know.
Here's the scent,
and the flute that
was used in its training.
Wait for the right
situation, and use it well,
to kill Itadori.
It might get hunted down
before we can use it, though.
[Yoshinobu] Don't worry.
It's been trained to
keep quiet and lay low
until the flute is blown.
(off key music)
I know Kamo.
He probably placed
the scent on Itadori
the moment they made
contact and the feed cut out.
It's easy enough for him to do
if he mixes his blood with it.
If the boy's fighting Todo,
he won't come out unscathed.
So, if Itadori's attacked
by a semi-first-grade
the moment after the fight,
he'll surely die!
You're right, Iori.
I'm worried about Miwa.
You should go to her quickly.
(suspenseful music)
[Toge] Kelp.
(footsteps approaching)
(spirit slobbering)
(Toge gasps)
(spirit stabbed)
(spirit rolls)
(footsteps approaching)
(Toge steps back)
(indistinct chanting)
Yellow fin. Tuna.
Prawn roe.
(suspenseful music)
Well then.
Looks like it's time
for us to go to work.
Let's make us a
custom coat rack!
Gojo's about a hundred
and ninety centimeters tall,
isn't he?
I'd say that's the
perfect size coat rack!
(transition music)
(rising music)
(Noritoshi cries)
Why is it everyone always
treats my mom so awful?
[Clan Woman] Because
she's a slutty concubine.
But then why is
everyone so good to me?
Why did the clan
take me in as heir?
[Clan Woman] Because
your father's proper wife
didn't produce a son who
inherited the technique.
[Noritoshi] Then, as the
next head of the Kamo clan-
(cautious music)
(Noritoshi and Megumi grunting)
(suspenseful music)
(Megumi grunts)
[Noritoshi] Shikigami users
who can fight this well in
close combat are precious.
You've improved.
I'm glad to see it.
Why do you keep acting as if
there's some sort of
fellowship between us?
I'm sympathizing.
Before too long
you'll be supporting
one of the major clans.
So you should know I
intend to kill Yuji Itadori.
On Principal Gakuganji's orders?
Oh, no. I made this
decision for myself.
I'm aware what's at stake. I
didn't need to be ordered.
I believe it was
the correct call.
As the heir to the Kamo clan,
I must behave appropriately.
For my mother's sake!
You should be able
to understand that, too.
After all, you and
I are the same.
The hell we are.
All of a sudden, this guy's
not making any sense.
We are the same.
No, we're not.
You can save those
discussions for Maki.
'Cause as for me
I've no connection
with the Zen'in clan now.
And besides,
I don't believe I'm
necessarily in the right here.
No, hang on.
That's wrong.
What I was really
trying to say is
that I don't care if
I'm right or wrong.
I just have faith in my
own sense of morality.
I save people according
to my conscience.
And if you reject that,
well then.
(hopeful music)
Then we'll curse
each other.
(wall crashes in)
(shikigami croaks)
[Noritoshi] A shikigami?
He still had more?
(shikigami dissipates)
[Noritoshi] He used
the shikigami as a decoy
before releasing it!
[Megumi] This one really
burns through the cursed energy,
so I can only use it by itself.
I've only managed
to tame it recently.
Max Elephant.
(elephant trumpets)
(elephant whines)
[Noritoshi] It's a big
target! I'll strike first!
(water shoots)
[Noritoshi] Water?
(building crashes outwards)
[Noritoshi] It blew me
away with mass and pressure!
Open spaces are
bad! That one's next!
(energy charging)
Nue!
(bird cawing)
(Noritoshi groaning)
[Noritoshi's Mother]
If I stay here, Noritoshi,
I'll just be in your way.
[Noritoshi] I-
Blood Manipulation!
(bird cawing)
(packet exploding)
Crimson Binding!
I can't afford to lose!
I refuse to lose!
(loud explosion)
[Megumi] Huh?
[Both] What is that?
Inumaki!
(footsteps approaching)
Run away!
(bells ringing)
(Megumi and Noritoshi gasp)
(loud explosion)
(charms burning)
Huh?
Hm?
Is the game over?
They all burned red!
[Mei] That's odd.
My crows didn't see anything.
I'd love to say that
the students of
great teacher Gojo
exorcized them
all but I doubt it.
Remember they also burn red
for unregistered cursed energy.
So what are you thinking?
Are you suspecting
it's an outsider?
If that's the case,
it means Tengen's
barrier isn't working.
Whether it's because
of some outsider or not,
something unexpected
is happening here.
[Yoshinobu] They had
to have been fairly skilled
to have exorcized that.
But who was it?
I'm going to go see Tengen.
Satoru and Principal Gakuganji,
please protect the students.
Mei, it's best you
stay here and pinpoint
all the students' locations.
Stay in constant contact
with the other two.
Fully understood.
I look forward to
the bonus money.
(Satoru claps)
On your feet, Gramps!
You and I are taking a walk.
You just finished your
lunch, good to go?
(electronic music)
[Utahime] Let's hurry.
(running footsteps)
(Megumi gasps)
(doors explode)
-(muffled explosion)
-Huh?
They're really going
at it over there.
But you know,
those cursed spirits don't
leave anything behind
when they die,
and that's a problem.
(Juzo grunts)
How am I supposed to make
anything from those things?
(Juzo yells)
(hammer clangs)
Was that good enough?
Ah, I forgot about that.
Emerge from
darkness blacker still.
Purify that which is impure.
(energy builds)
Oh yeah, this is good.
Go time's almost here.
Coat rack's comin' soon!
(footsteps approaching)
(energy builds)
(Miwa snores)
(electronic music)
A veil?
Why now?
(footsteps approaching)
[Utahime] Gojo!
You should go ahead of us,
before the veil comes down!
No, no way.
[Utahime] Huh?
[Satoru] That veil's
practically complete.
They chose to focus on cursed
techniques over visual effect.
Damn, they're good.
(footsteps approaching)
[Satoru] Well.
Now that it's down, I
just need to break it.
(energy sparks)
-(energy explodes)
-(Satoru recoils)
[Satoru] Huh, what
is this odd feeling?
Hey!
Why is the veil
keeping you outside,
while it's allowing me to enter?
I get it.
Utahime, Gramps, you go ahead.
This barrier here
is designed to allow all
others to go in and out freely,
in exchange for just one thing.
Denying that to Gojo.
(Utahime gasps)
[Utahime] True, that
would explain everything.
But, if they're able
to use a barrier
to keep a specific
individual out-
They must have quite
the skilled curse user.
Uh-huh, all this confirms
their intel on us is good.
Go!
Get moving.
I don't know what
their end goal is here,
but if any of us
dies, then we lose.
(Utamine gasps)
[Utahime] What a
strong curse presence!
Don't tell me there's a
special-grade curse here!
-[Juzo] Hey, hey, hey!
-(Utahime gasps)
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Why isn't Satoru Gojo here?
[Yoshinobu] Curse user.
He's not the source
of this presence,
but he's still quite capable.
It looks like that
degenerate monk
managed to trick me somehow!
Utahime, go on ahead.
Protect the
students at all costs.
Avoid fighting unless
it can't be helped.
What're you trying to do?
The least you could do
is let me kill the woman!
I can't make anything
from your old hollow
bones and wrinkled skin!
(case rattles)
[Yoshinobu] Why
don't you kill me then?
(guitar plays)
And find out for
yourself if they're hollow!
Why don't you go have a
nap and some nice warm milk?
You old fart.
A cursed spirit at Jujutsu Tech?
Just who produced this veil?
Probably the curse user
who's working with it.
(Toge nods)
Hm? Do you know
something about this?
These're unregistered
special-grade cursed spirits.
And it looks like they're
working with a human, too.
Yes.
I think it's the special-grade
that attacked Gojo
a while ago.
Its appearance
matches the report.
Even from that guy's
drawing, I recognize it.
[Toge] Tuna with mayo.
[Megumi] You're right.
Let's call Gojo
and let him know.
What? Hold on!
Do you actually
understand what he means
when he says that stuff?
That's not important right now.
Our enemy might use a domain.
I'm thinking we should
retreat and join Gojo and the-
(Noritoshi gasps)
(phone breaks)
Don't move!
(curse grumbles)
(packet explodes)
Blood Manipulation!
Slicing Exorcism!
No damage?
(bird caws)
(energy explodes)
(Megumi grunts)
[Megumi] Damn!
It's really tough!
[Noritoshi] A sword?
Where's he been hiding
that thing all this time?
(indistinct chanting)
[Hanami] Stop
it, foolish children.
(Megumi gasps)
[Megumi] What is this?
I can't tell what it's
saying by the sound,
but I somehow
understand its meaning!
That's just creepy.
[Hanami] I merely wish to
protect this planet, that's all.
[Noritoshi] It's a curse
spouting nonsense! Don't listen!
This is on a whole
different level
than lower-grade cursed spirits.
[Hanami] The forests,
the oceans, and the sky
all weep so vehemently
that I can no longer stand it.
It's impossible to coexist
with humans any longer.
The earth knows
there are some humans
who are kind to the planet.
But how much does
that insignificant amount
of affection help?
[Megumi] It's established
its own language!
[Hanami] All
they desire is time.
[Megumi] Get
Inumaki out of here!
[Hanami] This planet
can shine blue once more,
given a bit of time.
(ground explodes)
[Hanami] Time without humans!
Please die and become sages!
(closing theme music)
(singing in Japanese)
[Mahito, Jougo, and
Hanami] Juju Stroll!
(upbeat music)
Hey!
Jougo!
You burned up Hanami's
flower bed again, huh?
Now Hanami's crying!
(Hanami cries)
Hmph.
Hanami?
Jougo sucks.
Let's strangle him.
My boyfriend's teacher
who I told you about?
Well,
he'll handle it.
[Hanami] No,
that's going too far.
(piano music)
(wind blowing)
(Hanami sighs)
(Hanami cries)
(Hanami screams)
[Hanami] This is a
slash-and-burn farm!
The soil!
It didn't have enough
nutrients even before this!
(upbeat music)
(Hanami gasps)
[Jougo] Hmph.
(Hanami whimpers)
(music fades out)
(rock music)
(rock music fades out)